

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am an enthusiastic public relations strategist with strong interpersonal skills and extensive experience directing PR campaigns. Desire a worthwhile and suitable position in Public Relations, offering proven success developing and implementing media strategies across traditional and digital channels to promote the brand's image.

PROFESSIONAL KEY SKILLS

- Coming with proven PR Skills, exceptional writing skills, and budgeting skills, to develop and implement strategic solutions using appropriate PR communication vehicles.
- Problem solver with excellent project and time management skills.
- Coming with strong social media knowledge, excellent communication skills, and expert knowledge
- Microsoft Excel and Word
- Quick learner and adaptable to new challenges
- Instrumental in developing and executing campaigns for several companies as well as brands along with their product launches.
- Ability to adapt to changing market, media as well as client needs in order to reach out to various stakeholders.

LANGUAGE KNOWN

English: Speak | Read | Write Bengali: Speak | Read | Write Hindi: Speak | Read | Write

GET IN TOUCH WITH ME

Mob.: +91 8335802828

Email: ankitachakraborty54@gmail.com Residential Address: 13 A1 Bay Tower,

Hiland Park Apartments,

1925 Chak Garia, Kolkata 700094

ANKITA CHAKRABORTY

Public Relation Executive

WORK EXPERIENCE

Public Relations Executive (Celebrity)

Jeet (Actor) | September, 2019 - till date

- A celebrity publicist oversees the public image and manages all media relations of a celebrity client, which can include famous actors, singers, authors, and sports stars.
- The PR has to know how to respond to media inquiries and calm down the public, while also coming up with strategies to get the celebrity positive media coverage.
- Typically coordinate publicity events and make sure the client knows where to go and what to do.
- A celebrity PR representative is also in charge of finding opportunities for celebrities to make public appearances. The PR representative should be constantly working on new angles and making new contacts that can help get the celebrity's name attached to worthwhile causes and special events.
- Responsibilities may include writing press releases, releasing statements, escorting clients on red carpets and attending press junkets
- Answer queries and acts as a liaison between the celebrity, journalists and the general public
- Celebrities have numerous social media accounts, including Facebook pages, Twitter profiles and even Instagram accounts.
 Social Media Management is a daily task

Public Relations Executive

Edelman India | September 2018 - April 2019

Intern - Social Marketing and Communications

World Wide Funds for Nature India | June 2018 - July 2018

Intern - Human Resource and Communication

The Oberoi Grand | April 2016 - June 2016

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

Christ University, 2018

Master's in applied Sociology with Public Relations

Lady Bra Bourne College, Calcutta University, 2016

Bachelors in Sociology

St. Thomas Girls School Kolkata, 2012

I.S.C. - Class 12

St. Thomas Girls School Kolkata, 2012

I.S.C.E. - Class 10